Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series XIV: Periodicals, 263154
  - Books and Publishing: February 12, 1997. April 30, 1997. August 6-12, 1997. November 12-18, 1997. February 11-17, 1998., 1997-1998; 12970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Downtown: Issue No 370, Dec 13, 1995-Jan 17, 1996, 1995-1996; 12964 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Get, Vol 1, No 5, undated; 12961 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Index: Jan-Feb 1998, 12958 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - OP: July-August 1982, 12950 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Voice Literary Supplement: No 59, Oct 1987; No 60, Nov 1987; No 62, Feb 1988, 1987, 1988; 12936 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series I: Correspondence, 12872
  - Abrams, Leonard, undated; 12931 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Cynthia, undated; 12930 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Atkins, Robert, undated; 12929 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Basinski, Michael, undated; 12928 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Berman, Rebecca, undated; 12927 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ben-Magid, Tam, undated; 12926 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Bowery, Zagreus, undated; 12925 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Bushyeager, Peter, undated; 12924 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cusimano, Mick, undated; 12923 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dijkstra, Sandra, undated; 12922 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fagin, Betsy, undated; 12921 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Finberg, Bonny, undated; 12920 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ganshaw, John E., undated; 12919 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Eidus, Janice, undated; 12918 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Errol Grimes Dance Group, undated; 12917 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Hata, Takashi, undated; 12916 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Holman, Bob, undated; 12915 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Huisman, Violaine, undated; 12914 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Jankowski, Matty, undated; 12913 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Jushi, undated; 12912 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Kaufman, Alan, undated; 12911 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 12910 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated; 12909 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Lamm, Gigi, undated; 12908 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Lev, Donald, undated; 12907 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Lifshin, Lyn, undated; 12906 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Lytle, Ellen, undated; 12905 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Manister, Diana, undated; 12904 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Martinson, Neil, undated; 12903 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Mitchell, Reverand Dr. Timothy P., undated; 12902 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Moore, Thurston, undated; 12901 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Myers, Holly, undated; 12900 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated; 12899 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Packer, Eve, undated; 12898 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Perez, Richard, undated; 12897 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 12896 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Preston, Jane, undated; 12895 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Rabinowitz, Jacob, undated; 12894 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Raff, Colin, undated; 12893 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Randall, Michael, undated; 12892 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Romo, Donna, undated; 12891 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Rossen, Anina, undated; 12890 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Savage, Tom, undated; 12889 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Scutti, Susan, undated; 12888 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Seweryn, Natalie, undated; 12887 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Sureff, Paul E., undated; 12886 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Swenson, Karen, undated; 12885 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Swiss, Rabbi Harold, undated; 12884 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Talbot, John, undated; 12883 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Tanselle, G. Thomas, undated; 12882 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated; 12881 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Topp, Mike, undated; 12880 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Transe, John J., undated; 12879 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Watson, Steve, undated; 12878 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Weinstein, Gail, undated; 12877 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Wheatstraw, P. D., undated; 12876 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Wuelfing, Howard, undated; 12875 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated; 12874 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Unidentified / Partial Name, undated; 12873 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series II: Manuscripts, 12833
  - Feast, Jim and Ron Kolm. Catalog for Roman Show of Himmelstein and Witz., undated; 12871 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Feast, Jim. Poetry., undated; 12870 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Finberg, Bonny. In the City of Barking Dogs., undated; 12869 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Finberg, Bonny. Poetry., undated; 12868 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Golden, Mike. For Art's Sake: A True Life Screen Trade Lesson., undated; 12867 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Hardin, Rob. Poetry., undated; 12866 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Huberman, David. Short Stories., undated; 12865 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Kolm, Ron. Poetry., undated; 12864 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Kolm, Ron. A Trail of Beer and Poetry: The Unbearables Journey through the Dive Bars of New York City., undated; 12863 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Litzky, Tsaurah. My Gladiola-A Memoir., undated; 12862 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Litzky, Tsaurah. Poetry., undated; 12861 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Maynard, Joe. Poetry., undated; 12860 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Mesmer, Sharon. Poetry., undated; 12859 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Nostrand, Jenifer. Poetry., undated; 12858 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Nufer, Doug. In the End, There Was No End., undated; 12857 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Nufer, Doug. The River Boys., undated; 12856 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Padua, JosPoetry., undated; 12855 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Penn, John. Fear of Milk., undated; 12854 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Pirolli, John Paul. Poetry., undated; 12853 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus. Roughhouse., undated; 12852 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Ruthowski, Thaddeus. Short Fiction., undated; 12851 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Savage, Tom. Poetry., undated; 12850 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Schein, Lorraine. Poetry., undated; 12849 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Scutti, Susan. Shhhhhh., undated; 12848 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Sparrow. Poetry., undated; 12847 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Topp, Mike. Chinese Chipmunk., undated; 12846 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Topp, Mike. I Used to Be Ashamed of My Striped Face., undated; 12845 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Topp, Mike. A Midwestern Romance., undated; 12844 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Topp, Mike. Poetry., undated; 12843 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Vitale, Alfred. Poetry and Short Fiction., undated; 12842 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Vitale, Alfred. Yorkville., undated; 12841 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Watson, Carl. Poetry., undated; 12840 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol. Honeymoon in the Meat Packing District., undated; 12839 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol. Poetry., undated; 12838 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Witz, Bob. Poetry., undated; 12837 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Unknown. Lolita on the 9:25., undated; 12836 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Zummer, Thomas. Portraits of Robots., undated; 12835 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Zummer, Thomas. Projection and Dis/embodiment: Genealogies of the Virtual., undated; 12834 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series III: The Unbearables, 12811
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Legal Issue. Issue 11, 3/5/2000., 12832 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine, Issue II - Production files, 262683 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Legal Issue-Production Files, undated; 12831 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Conspiracy Issue, Issue 13, 2/25/2001-, 12830 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Help Yourself!-book cover, undated; 12828 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Unbearables, undated; 12827 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Tribes Gallery reading, 5/18/2000, 12826 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - La Perla Garden reading, 8/3/2000, 12825 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - DaVinci Gallery reading, 8/13/2000, 12824 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Back Beat Festival reading, 10/5/2000, 12823 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ultra Violet Cafeading, 3/2/2001, 12822 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival-Materials, 4/2001, 12821 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival "911" reading, 4/1/2001, 12820 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Peoples Poetry Gathering, 4/1/2001, 12819 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Bryant Park reading, 5/7/2001, 12818 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Back Fence reading, 5/13/2001, 12817 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - La Perla Garden reading, 5/25/2001, 12816 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival 2001-Catalogue, 12815 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Unbearables Arts Festival 2001-Mock-up of Catalogue, 12814 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Boston Newspaper Reviews of Buddah, undated; 12813 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Article re: site of Unbearables Arts Festival in New Jersey, undated; 12812 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series IV: Subject Files, 12710
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists, 12737
    - Anthony, William, undated; 12810 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Basinski, Michael, undated; 12809 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Beatty, Paul, undated; 12808 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Blagg, Max, undated; 12807 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Branca, Glenn, undated; 12806 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Brown, Ken, undated; 12805 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Bush, Catherine, undated; 12804 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Cabico, Regie, undated; 12803 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Coleman, Daniel, undated; 12802 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Corso, Gregory, undated; 12801 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Crawford, John, undated; 12800 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Creeley, Robert, undated; 12799 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Crisp, Quentin, undated; 12798 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Cusimano, Mick, undated; 12797 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - D'Agostino, John, undated; 12796 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Delany, Samuel, undated; 12795 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Deyab, Larry, undated; 12794 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Dlugos, Tim, undated; 12793 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Dobkin, Jess, undated; 12792 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Downes, Rackstraw, undated; 12791 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Dr. Long, undated; 12790 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Eggers, David, undated; 12789 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - English, Ron, undated; 12788 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Estep, Maggie, undated; 12787 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Feast, Jim, undated; 12786 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - FLY, undated; 12785 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated; 12784 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - Gilbert, Sky, undated; 12783 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, undated; 12782 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - Giorno, John, undated; 12781 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - Goldberg, Roselee, undated; 12780 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - Hardin, Rob, undated; 12779 (Box 22, Folder 61)
    - Huberman, David, undated; 12778 (Box 22, Folder 62)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated; 12777 (Box 22, Folder 63)
    - Kaufman, Alan, undated; 12776 (Box 22, Folder 64)
    - KAZ, undated; 12775 (Box 22, Folder 65)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 12774 (Box 22, Folder 66)
    - Kostabi, Mark, undated; 12773 (Box 22, Folder 67)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 12772 (Box 22, Folder 68)
    - Kuper, Peter, undated; 12771 (Box 22, Folder 69)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated; 12770 (Box 22, Folder 70)
    - Leary, Mary, undated; 12769 (Box 22, Folder 71)
    - Lida, David, undated; 12768 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Lytle, Ellen, undated; 12767 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Mazza, Cris, undated; 12766 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, undated; 12765 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - Nersesian, Arthur, undated; 12764 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Nester, Daniel, undated; 12763 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, undated; 12762 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Nostrand, Jenifer, undated; 12761 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - Nufer, Doug, undated; 12760 (Box 22, Folder 80)
    - Olsen, Lance, undated; 12759 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 12758 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Pritchard, A. A., undated; 12757 (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Raff, Colin, undated; 12756 (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - Reed, Halcomb, undated; 12755 (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - Rosenbaum, Ron, undated; 12754 (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated; 12753 (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - Scutti, Susan, undated; 12752 (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated; 12751 (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - Sparrow, undated; 12750 (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated; 12749 (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - Tobocman, Seth, undated; 12748 (Box 22, Folder 92)
    - Ulin, David, undated; 12747 (Box 22, Folder 93)
    - Vitale, Alfred, undated; 12746 (Box 22, Folder 94)
    - Watson, Carl, undated; 12745 (Box 22, Folder 95)
    - Wechsler, Arnold, undated; 12744 (Box 22, Folder 96)
    - Weiss, Tom, undated; 12743 (Box 22, Folder 97)
    - Wheeler, Susan, undated; 12742 (Box 22, Folder 98)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated; 12741 (Box 22, Folder 99)
    - Wortsman, Peter, undated; 12740 (Box 22, Folder 100)
    - XYZ, Emily, undated; 12739 (Box 22, Folder 101)
    - Zummer, Tom, undated; 12738 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects, 12711
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 12736 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Art Forum, Berlin, undated; 12735 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Autonomedia, undated; 12734 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Barnum and Buddah Poetry Circus, undated; 12733 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Bloomsday reading of Ulysses, undated; 12732 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, undated; 12731 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Circus Amok, undated; 12730 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Coliseum Books, undated; 12729 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Downtown Collection, Fales Library, undated; 12728 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Feminist Art, undated; 12727 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Fire of Prometheus, undated; 12726 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Gargoyle Magazine, undated; 12725 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Gathering of the Tribes, undated; 12724 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - La Mama, undated; 12723 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Low-Tech Press, undated; 12722 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Medicinal Purposes, undated; 12721 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Museum of Modern Art, undated; 12720 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Performing Garage, undated; 12719 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Poet's House, undated; 12718 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Public Illumination Magazine, undated; 12717 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - PS 122, undated; 12716 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Spoleto Festival, undated; 12715 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - The Strand, undated; 12714 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Ten Pell Books, undated; 12713 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - WFMU, undated; 12712 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series V: Photographs, 12705
  - Ides of March 2000 at The Homestead Bar, photos by Lydia Tomkiw, 12709 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Photos of Chez Rollo assembled for New Observations, undated; 12708 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Bryant Park Event, undated; 12707 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - McManus Party, 12/21/1999; Reading at CBGB's, 1/1/2000, 1999, 2000; 12706 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Accretions 2000-2001 - Series VI: Announcements, 12474
  - Subseries A: Readings, 12612
    - 2A Bar, undated; 12704 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - 5C Cultural Center, undated; 12703 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 12702 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Allen, Roberta, undated; 12701 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Andrews, Cynthia, undated; 12700 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Angel Orensanz Foundation, undated; 12699 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Art in General, undated; 12698 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Back Fence Poetry Reading, undated; 12697 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Barnard, undated; 12696 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Barnes & Noble, undated; 12695 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Bergen Street Beat, undated; 12694 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Bluestockings, undated; 12693 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Bogosian, Eric, undated; 12692 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Books by Artists, undated; 12691 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Broadsides, undated; 12690 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Brooklyn Lyceum, undated; 12689 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Buhl's Loft, undated; 12688 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - By Herself: Women Reclaim Poetry, undated; 12687 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - CBGB, undated; 12686 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - CCS Reading Series, undated; 12685 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Cedar Tavern, undated; 12684 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Charas Community Center, undated; 12683 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Chelsea Lounge, undated; 12682 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated; 12681 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Chico West Garden, undated; 12680 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - China Club, undated; 12679 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Clovis Press, undated; 12678 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Cornelia Street Cafunittitle>, undated; 12677 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Consulate General of France, undated; 12676 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Den of Sin, undated; 12675 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - DIA Center for the Arts, undated; 12674 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Dixon Place, undated; 12673 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - First Unitarian Church, undated; 12672 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Frank's Lounge, undated; 12671 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Galapagos, undated; 12670 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Gathering of the Tribes, undated; 12669 (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - Gershwin Hotel, undated; 12668 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Good World Bar and Bar, undated; 12667 (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - Greenwich Village Bistro, undated; 12666 (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Groove, undated; 12665 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Housing Works, undated; 12664 (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - Internet Cafunittitle>, undated; 12663 (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Joe's Pub, undated; 12662 (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - KGB Bar, undated; 12661 (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Knitting Factory, undated; 12660 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - La Perla Garden, undated; 12659 (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Locus Media, undated; 12658 (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Lungfull!, undated; 12657 (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Lida, David, undated; 12656 (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - Life, undated; 12655 (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Little Theater, undated; 12654 (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - Living Room, undated; 12653 (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Lotus Center, undated; 12652 (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - Lower East Side Festival, undated; 12651 (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, undated; 12650 (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - Mamma Cassie's Coffee Shop, undated; 12649 (Box 23, Folder 85)
    - Mid-Manhattan Library, undated; 12648 (Box 23, Folder 86)
    - Moroccan Star, undated; 12647 (Box 23, Folder 87)
    - Museum of the City of New York, undated; 12646 (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Myles, Eileen, undated; 12645 (Box 23, Folder 89)
    - New York Performance Works, undated; 12644 (Box 23, Folder 90)
    - New York Press, undated; 12643 (Box 23, Folder 91)
    - Nuyorican Poets' Cafe, undated; 12642 (Box 23, Folder 92)
    - Ohm, undated; 12641 (Box 23, Folder 93)
    - Parkside Lounge, undated; 12640 (Box 23, Folder 94)
    - Poets and Writers, undated; 12639 (Box 23, Folder 95)
    - Poets House, undated; 12638 (Box 23, Folder 96)
    - Poet to Poet, undated; 12637 (Box 23, Folder 97)
    - Reading Between A and B, undated; 12636 (Box 23, Folder 98)
    - Reading Room, undated; 12635 (Box 23, Folder 99)
    - Rightbank Cafe, undated; 12634 (Box 23, Folder 100)
    - Schein, Lorraine, undated; 12633 (Box 23, Folder 101)
    - Segue Space, undated; 12632 (Box 23, Folder 102)
    - Seven Stories Press, undated; 12631 (Box 23, Folder 103)
    - Sideshow, undated; 12630 (Box 23, Folder 104)
    - S. J. South Bar, undated; 12629 (Box 23, Folder 105)
    - Skanky Possum Press, undated; 12628 (Box 23, Folder 106)
    - Slaymakers, Bob, undated; 12627 (Box 23, Folder 107)
    - Spa, undated; 12626 (Box 23, Folder 108)
    - Splendid Bar and Cafe, undated; 12625 (Box 23, Folder 109)
    - Stalke Galleri, undated; 12624 (Box 23, Folder 110)
    - State of Art Gallery, undated; 12623 (Box 23, Folder 111)
    - St. Mark's Church, undated; 12622 (Box 23, Folder 112)
    - Teachers & Writers Collaborative, undated; 12621 (Box 23, Folder 113)
    - Temple Bar, undated; 12620 (Box 23, Folder 114)
    - Thread Waxing Space, undated; 12619 (Box 23, Folder 115)
    - Tomkiw, Lydia, undated; 12618 (Box 23, Folder 116)
    - Tower Books, undated; 12617 (Box 23, Folder 117)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated; 12616 (Box 23, Folder 118)
    - Two Girls, undated; 12615 (Box 23, Folder 119)
    - Yakity Yak, undated; 12614 (Box 23, Folder 120)
    - Zinc Bar, undated; 12613 (Box 23, Folder 121)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements, 12475
    - 304 Art, undated; 12611 (Box 23, Folder 122)
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 12610 (Box 23, Folder 123)
    - A.I.R. Gallery, undated; 12609 (Box 23, Folder 124)
    - Alliance for the Arts, undated; 12608 (Box 23, Folder 125)
    - Art Resources Transfer Inc., undated; 12607 (Box 23, Folder 126)
    - Beaver Group, undated; 12606 (Box 23, Folder 127)
    - Berenberg Gallery, undated; 12605 (Box 23, Folder 128)
    - Bluestockings, undated; 12604 (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - Brooklyn Artist Bookmakers, undated; 12603 (Box 23, Folder 130)
    - Bound & Unbound, undated; 12602 (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - Brecht Forum, undated; 12601 (Box 23, Folder 132)
    - Bronfman Center for Jewish Student Life, undated; 12600 (Box 23, Folder 133)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, undated; 12599 (Box 23, Folder 134)
    - Bruce Weber's No Chance Ensemble, undated; 12598 (Box 23, Folder 135)
    - Bucknell Art Gallery, undated; 12597 (Box 23, Folder 136)
    - Carbon, undated; 12596 (Box 23, Folder 137)
    - CBGB's Gallery, undated; 12595 (Box 23, Folder 138)
    - Century Center, undated; 12594 (Box 23, Folder 139)
    - Cheetah, undated; 12593 (Box 23, Folder 140)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated; 12592 (Box 23, Folder 141)
    - China Club, undated; 12591 (Box 23, Folder 142)
    - Church of St. Andrew, undated; 12590 (Box 23, Folder 143)
    - Church, Tom, undated; 12589 (Box 23, Folder 144)
    - Circus Amok, undated; 12588 (Box 23, Folder 145)
    - Club Europa, undated; 12587 (Box 23, Folder 146)
    - Cokkie Snoei, undated; 12586 (Box 23, Folder 147)
    - Dobbin Books, undated; 12585 (Box 23, Folder 148)
    - Collective Unconscious, undated; 12584 (Box 23, Folder 149)
    - Cooler, undated; 12583 (Box 23, Folder 150)
    - Cpop Gallery, undated; 12582 (Box 23, Folder 151)
    - Cream, undated; 12581 (Box 23, Folder 152)
    - Currican Theatre, undated; 12580 (Box 23, Folder 153)
    - dfn Gallery, undated; 12579 (Box 23, Folder 154)
    - Den of Sin, undated; 12578 (Box 23, Folder 155)
    - Dia Center for the Arts, undated; 12577 (Box 23, Folder 156)
    - Digitas, undated; 12576 (Box 23, Folder 157)
    - Dixon Place, undated; 12575 (Box 23, Folder 158)
    - Double Happiness, undated; 12574 (Box 23, Folder 159)
    - Downtown Music Gallery, undated; 12573 (Box 23, Folder 160)
    - Dumba, undated; 12572 (Box 23, Folder 161)
    - Editions Fawbush, undated; 12571 (Box 23, Folder 162)
    - Egizio's Project, undated; 12570 (Box 23, Folder 163)
    - Exhibition Space 156, undated; 12569 (Box 23, Folder 164)
    - Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, undated; 12568 (Box 23, Folder 165)
    - Fad, undated; 12567 (Box 23, Folder 166)
    - Film Forum, undated; 12566 (Box 23, Folder 167)
    - Fleischer Art Memorial, undated; 12565 (Box 23, Folder 168)
    - Fordham University Law Building, undated; 12564 (Box 23, Folder 169)
    - Foundry Theatre, undated; 12563 (Box 23, Folder 170)
    - Franklin Furnace Archive, Inc., undated; 12562 (Box 23, Folder 171)
    - Frederieke Taylor, undated; 12561 (Box 23, Folder 172)
    - Galapagos Performance Space, undated; 12560 (Box 23, Folder 173)
    - Gallery@49, undated; 12559 (Box 23, Folder 174)
    - Gathering of the Tribes Gallery, undated; 12558 (Box 23, Folder 175)
    - Geoffrey Young Gallery, undated; 12557 (Box 23, Folder 176)
    - Grady Alexis Gallery, undated; 12556 (Box 23, Folder 177)
    - Granary Books, undated; 12555 (Box 23, Folder 178)
    - Green Door, undated; 12554 (Box 23, Folder 179)
    - Greene-Naftali Gallery, undated; 12553 (Box 23, Folder 180)
    - Grey Art Gallery, undated; 12552 (Box 23, Folder 181)
    - Grolier Club, undated; 12551 (Box 23, Folder 182)
    - Guggenheim Museum, undated; 12550 (Box 23, Folder 183)
    - Hallway, undated; 12549 (Box 23, Folder 184)